还有三分钟反应堆就要爆炸了
We've got 3 minutes till the reactor blows,
我们逃不掉了
we’re never gonna make it!
你得赶快逃命  保命要紧
"You've got to get out of here! Save yourself!"
不行  我不会扔下你
"l won't leave you. "
别管我  我是机器人
"Don't worry about me. l'm a robot.
我只是一台机器
l'm just a machine!"
-对我来说不是  -天啊
- "No, you're not. Not to me. " - Oh, my God.
-怎样  -我简直太有才华了
- What? - l am extremely talented.
对  你确很棒
Yeah. You're great.
好  我们从...
Okay, let's take it from...
不是  我真的超会演的
No, l mean, l was really acting my ass off.
我觉得我也很不错
l thought l was pretty good, too.
你是很不错  只不过不是我
Yeah, you're solid. You're just no me.
我看就先这样吧
You know what? l think that's enough for now.
我不想排练过头
l don't want to be over-rehearsed.
没关系  我自己演
Fine. l'll do it without you!
我不需要你或任何人
l don't need you or anybody else!
我会靠我自己成功
l'm gonna make it on my own!
等着瞧  都给我等着瞧
You'll see! You'll all see!
你要去试什么镜
So uh, what’s this thing you’re auditioning for?
是一部新影集
lt's a new TV show.
我的角色叫麦克·麦可维利  也叫麦克
l'm up for the part of Mac, Machiavelli, or "Mac" !
我是个侦探
l'm a detective
和我的机器人拍档一起打击犯罪
and l solve crimes with the help of my robot partner.
他是人性化
He's a computerized humanoid...
电脑电子秘密杀手
...electronically enhanced secret enforcer.
简称"起司"
Or "C.H.E.E.S.E."
麦克与起司[起司通心面]
So Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.?
那就是剧名啊
That's the title!
幸好缩写刚好是起司  不然我记不住
They lucked out that the initials spell "cheese. "
真是幸好
That is lucky.
乔伊  要是你拿到这个角色
So Joey, if you get this, you're gonna be, like...
就有你自己的影集了
...the star of your own TV show.
你就会被称为大起司[汉堡]
l mean, you'll be like the "Big Cheese"
或是大麦克[巨无霸汉堡]
or the "Big Mac. "
都是你的最爱耶
Hey, you love those!
别抱  太大期望  应该没那么好运
Well, don’t get your hopes up, because probably not gonna happen.
你为什么要这么说  乔瑟夫
Now-now, why would you say that Joseph?
拜托  由我主演的影集耶
Well, l mean, come on, guys. My own TV show?
-我都不知道我行不行  -我行
-I just...I don't know if l'm good enough. - l am.
乔伊  你在说什么啊  你是个很棒的演员
Joey, what are you talking about? You’re a terrific actor.
-真的吗  -你怎么能这么问
- You really think so? - How can you even ask that question?
-她真漂亮  -对  人也很好
- She's pretty. - Yeah. And she's really nice too.
她教我怎么面对镜头
She taught me all about how to work with cameras...
和闻屁演技法
...and "smell the fart" acting.
-什么  -你说什么
- l'm sorry. What? - Excuse me?
因为在短时间内要背很多台词
lt's like you got so many lines to learn so fast...
有时得停下来想下一句
that sometimes you need time to remember your next one.
所以在你想的时候
So while you're thinking of it,
要来个大停顿  表情故作严肃
you take this pause where you look intense.
就像这样
You know, like this:
懂了
Okay.
该我了  该我了
Here's my scene! Here's my scene!
华勒斯太太  我是拉莫瑞医生
Mrs. Wallace? l'm Dr. Drake Ramorey,
令妹的神经外科医生
your sister's surgeon.
令妹得了一种...
You sister is suffering from a....
伊娃
Well, Eva,
我们有不错的进展
we've done some excellent work here.
老实说
And l would have to say
你的困扰很清楚
your problem is quite clear.
你只是想要一个老二
All you want is a tinkle
你是在忌妒男人
What you envy's a schwang
你想要拿它来撒尿
A thing through which you can tinkle
或是把玩  或是挂在那边
Or play with or simply let hang
我演艾尔·帕西诺的屁股
l play Al Pacino's butt.
好吗
All right?
他进去淋浴  然后我就是他的屁股
He goes into the shower and then, l'm his butt.
-天啊  -别这样  伙计们
- Oh, my God. - Come on, you guys.
这部电影  艾尔·帕西诺主演  很不得了
This is a movie and Al Pacino's in it, and that's big!
的确很棒  你当之无愧  努力了这么久
lt's terrific. You deserve this. After years of struggling...
终于可以"屁美"别人了
...you've finally cracked your way into show business.
好  你们笑吧  我不在乎
Okay, Okay, fine, make jokes. l don't care.
这是我演艺事业的重大突破
This is a big break for me.
没错  你说得很对
No. You're right, you're right, it is.
你会找我们去看你"精屁"的演出吗
So, you gonna invite us to the big opening?
好  我要走了  祝我好运
All right, l'm out of here. Wish me luck.
加油  加油  我们祝你好运
Good luck, good luck We all wish you good luck
随便啦
Yeah, whatever.
该你了
It's your turn.
我们有在玩喔
Oh, are we playing this?
试镜结果如何
How'd the audition go?
很烂
Terrible.
我把台词都念坏了  我不该当演员的
I messed up every line. l shouldn't even be an actor.
等等  你是不是
Wait a minute, are you doing that thing
又在假装不顺利
where you pretend it didn’t go well
其实获得成功的事实吗
but it really did go well?
-对  有吓着你们吗  -完全吓着了
- Yeah, did l fool you? - Totally!
-所以很顺利吗  -顺利得不得了
- So it did go well? - it went amazingly well!
-太好了  -剩我跟另两个人  三选一
- Great! - lt's down to me and two other guys.
我认识他们  那两个人都很厉害
And I know both of them, they’re really good
一个是在过敏广告里
One of them is the guy from those allergy commercials
被巨花追来追去的那个人
who’s always getting chased by those big flowers...
我好喜欢那个人
Oh, l love that guy!
你这是干嘛
What are you doing?
我这是干嘛呢
What am l doing?
我好紧张
l'm so nervous, you know?
明天下午五点才要复试
The callback is tomorrow at 5:00.
-我的头好像要爆炸了  -你的头早该爆了
- l feel like my head's gonna explode. - Well, it is overdue.
放心  你一定没问题
Look, don’t worry. Okay? You’re gonna be fine.
压力真的好大
But it's so much pressure.
无意冒犯  但你们的工作很不同
I mean no offense, but what you guys do is very different.
我不知道你们能不能体会
l don't know if you'd understand.
是啊  我们的工作都没有压力
Yeah, none of the rest of us have to deal with pressure at our jobs.
是的  弗兰  我知道现在几点了
Yes, Fran. I know what time it is,
但是我对"系周量"很不满意
but l'm looking at the Wenus and l'm not happy.
我在撕生菜
Well, l'm tearing the lettuce.
-它脏吗  -放心  我会洗的
- ls it dirty? - Oh-oh, no no don't worry, I'm gonna wash it.
不必  我喜欢脏[下流]的
Don't. l like it dirty.
你决定就好
That's your call.
你接下来要做什么
So what are you going to do next?
我要切蕃茄
l thought l'd cut up the tomatoes.
它们还硬吗
Are they firm?
-还不差  -你确定它们没有变坏
- They're all right. - You sure they haven't gone bad?
-你确定它们没有很坏很不乖吗
You sure they're not very, very bad?
-它们还好  -你会把它们切得很漂亮吗
- No, really. They're okay. - You gonna slice them real nice?
其实我想切丝
Actually, l was gonna do them julienne.
我要走了
l'm out of here.
莫妮卡  我要辞职
l'm quitting.
我刚帮一个老女人挤进丁字裤
l just helped an 81-year-old woman put on a thong...
结果她没买
...and she didn't even buy it.
我要辞职
I'm telling you. l'm quitting. That's it.
我现在就要跟老板说
l'm talking to my boss right now.
我要  我要我要我要...
Yes I am! Yes I am! Yes I am! Yes I am! Yes I am!
再见  听到留言请回电
Bye. Call me when you get this message.
怎么了
Well, what happened?
他来按摩  本来都没事  后来...
Well, he came in for a massage, and everything was fine until...
天啊
Oh, my God.
然后突然间毛手毛脚成了小事
And all of a sudden, his hands weren't the problem anymore.
-那里有没有  -搭帐棚都绰绰有余
- Was it? - Boy Scouts could've camped under there.
你吃了我的三明治吗
You ate my sandwich?
这只是个错误  谁都可能会犯
It was a simple mistake. It could happen to anyone.
是吗
Really?
你别激动
Now calm down.
来我的办公室找  垃圾桶里可能还有
Come look in my office. Some of it may still be in the trash.
-什么  -它很大
- What? - Well, it was quite large.
我只好扔掉一大半
l had to throw most of it away.
你...你扔掉我的三明治了吗
You threw my sandwich away?
我的三明治
My sandwich?
My sandwich!
我好想拿到这个角色
lt's just, l want this part so much, you know?
要是我没拿到
lf l don't get this part,
我就再也不吃起司通心面
l'm never gonna eat macaroni and cheese again.
不  我没说  我瞎说的
No, l didn't say that. That doesn't count.
别这样  我又不是搬去欧洲
Come on, guys. lt's not like l moved to Europe.
我只是搬到对面
l just moved across the hall.
我们也想经常请你们来坐
And we would have you over all the time...
但是莫妮卡会过敏
...if it weren't for Monica's allergies.
没错  我骗不了你们
You're right, l could never lie to you.
她讨厌你们
She hates you.
要接吗
Should l get that?
你好
Hello?
乔伊现在不在  你要留言吗
No, Joey's not here right now. Can l take a message?
好  试镜从五点改到两点半
Yeah, okay. So the audition's been moved from 5:00 to 2:30?
好的  再见
Okay, great. Bye.
-你还没穿衣服[着装]  -我又裸体了吗
- Aren't you dressed yet? - Am l naked again?
我们十五分钟后要去见我爸妈
We’re supposed to meet my parents in 15 minutes.
我只是在跟它们聊天  你看他们嘛
OK. l was just talking to the guys. Look at them.
它们可以去拜访我们吗
ls it okay if they come visit?
那我的过敏怎么办
What about my allergies?
也对  你会过敏
Right. Your allergies.
都是她  她讨厌你们
All her. She hates you.
真棒  漂亮
Yes! All right.
要是这些小人能变
How cool would it be
成真人大小该有多酷
if you could watch a life- size version of this?
-该有多过瘾  -跟足球一样过瘾
- l mean, how crazy would that be? - As crazy as soccer?
你好
Hello?
你在说什么  五点才试镜啊
What are you talking about? The audition's at 5.
没有人告诉我
Well, nobody told me.
你跟谁说的
Who'd you talk to?
没事了
Never mind.
这样你看不懂吗
You mean you didn't get it from this?
那个过敏人入选了  谢谢你啊
The allergy guy got the part. Thanks.
也许还可以补救
Maybe we can fix it.
我们可以送超大的巨花去吓他
Maybe we can send him some big flowers and scare him!
你怎么能这样呢  钱德勒
How could you do this to me, Chandler?
这个角色可以让我的事业起死回生
This part could've turned my career around.
是我不好
l messed up, okay?
对不起  我真的错了
l'm sorry. l really messed up.
你都不住这里了
You don't even live here anymore,
干嘛接我的电话  我有答录机
What are you doing answering my phone? I have my machine!
那是我买给你的
Which l bought for you.
还教你怎么使用  你以为它是影印机
Taught you how to use it. You thought it was a copier.
我愿意尽全力挽救这个错误  好吗
lf there was anything l could do, l'd do it, OK?
但是人起码可以犯一次错
Everybody's allowed one mistake, right?
他可以送我录影机
You know he coulda gotten me a VCR,
可以送我高尔夫球具
he coulda gotten me a set of golf clubs
可是他偏偏要送我"倒女人胃口表"
But no, he has to get me the "Woman Repeller. "
一个废五金行里最丑的东西
The eyesore from the "Liberace House of Crap!"
-没那么严重  -你站着说话不腰疼
- lt's not that bad. - Easy for you to say.
你又不必带着某个老粗淘汰的金饰到处跑
You don't have to sport a reject from the "Mr. T" collection.
钱德勒  钱德勒
Chandler, Chandler.
"我真同情戴这个手饰的人  真的"
l pity the fool who puts on my jewelry! l do! l do!
"我真同情戴这个..."  你好
l pity the fool that.... Hi.
你昨天晚归  凯西和我聊了起来
When you were late last night, Kathy and l were talking and...
事情演变到后来就...
...one thing led to another and....
就什么  你跟她上床了吗
And what? Did you sleep with her?
没有  我只是吻了她
No! No, l just kissed her.
什么  那样更糟
What? That's even worse!
-怎么会更糟呢  -我不知道  都一样啦
- How is that worse?! - l don't know! But it's the same!
你说得对  我无话可说  我彻底越线了
You're right. l have no excuses. I was totally over the line.
越线
Over the line?
你越线远到你甚至根本看不到那条线了
You're so far past the line that you can't even see it!
那条线都会说你过分
The line is a dot to you!
我不是要你奇迹式的原谅我
Look, l'm not saying you should magically forgive me.
但你也不完美  你也做过错误的判断
But you're not perfect. You've made errors in judgment.
举个例子
Name one!
怎么回事
What happened?
天啊  他答应不拿沙发椅的
Man! He promised he wouldn't take the chairs!
他娘的发生了什么事
What the hell happened!?
你怎么会被关进去  我们的东西呢
How were you locked in? And where the hell's all of our stuff?
有一个人来看柜子
This guy came to look at the unit...
他觉得它塞不下一个成年人
...and he didn't think it was big enough to fit a grown man.
所以你就自愿进去了吗
So you got in voluntarily?
人家想把柜子卖出去嘛
l was trying to make a sale!
要是让我碰上他  你猜我会怎样
Oh man! lf l ever run into him again, know what l'll do?
把屁股翘起来任人处置吗
Bend over?
她来了
There's Lori.
记住  不准交换
OK, now, remember, no trading.
美女是你的  失恋女是我的
You get the pretty one, l get the mess.
乔伊
Hi, Joey.
他就是你带来的人啊
Well, well. Look what you brought.
你又带了谁来
And what did you bring?
她在寄放外套
She's checking her coat.
乔伊  我要去把我手上的出租车味洗掉
Joey, l'm gonna go wash the cab smell off my hands.
帮我叫一杯白葡萄酒  帮珍妮丝叫一杯红酒
Will you get me a white Zinfandel and a glass of red for Janice.
珍妮丝
Janice?
Janice??
我  的  老天啊
Oh, my God!
乔伊的裁缝吃我豆腐
Joey's tailor took advantage of me.
什么
What?
不可能  我找他做了十二年了衣服
No way. l've been going to the guy for 12 years.
拜托啦  他说要量裤管内侧
Come on. You said he'd do my inseam...
然后他举起我的脚  那绝对是...
and he ran his hand up my leg, and then, there was definite...
怎样
What?
口交的姿势
Cupping.
裤子就是那样量的
That's how they do pants!
罗斯  你告诉他
Ross, will you tell him?
裁缝不都是这样量裤子的吗
lsn't that how a tailor measures pants?
是啊  是啊  那是在监狱
Yes, yes, it is. ln prison!
我只让你举一个
l said name one!
我居然这么粗心  我真白痴
l can't believe l did this. What an idiot!
别再自责了
Stop beating yourself up.
人都会犯错  这是难免的
People make mistakes. These things happen.
你没有忘记帮我记过留言吧
There aren't any messages you've forgotten to give me, honey?
你真的是不太会帮人记留言嘛
Apparently, you're not very good at it.
-你们觉得他会原谅我吗  -当然会
- Do you think he'll ever forgive me? - Of course he will.
但钱德勒  最重要的是  你得原谅自己
But Chandler, the important thing is that you forgive yourself.
-其实我已经原谅自己了  -这么快
- You know what, l kind of have. - Already?
你犯的错蛮严重的呢
That was pretty bad what you did.
他会原谅你的
Y’know what? He will forgive you.
我接电话时
And I like to bring a pad with me
都会带便条纸  以免...
when I go answer the phone just in case…
你没看到他气成什么样子
You didn't see how mad he was, you know?
我保证他一定会原谅你的
l'm sure he'll forgive you.
我们都有这种经验
Look, we've all been there, you know?
吵架  和解  就是这样
You fight, you make up. it’s just the way it works.
这段感情会破裂是两个人的错
lt took two people to break up this relationship!
对  你和影印店那个女的
Yeah! You and that girl from that copy place,
你昨天就表明愿意负责
which yesterday you took full responsibility for!!
我不知道我负的是什么责
l didn't know what l was taking responsibility for, OK?
-我没把信看完  -什么
- l didn't finish the whole letter. - What?
-我睡着了  -你居然睡着了
- l fell asleep. - You fell asleep?
当时是早上5点半
lt was 5:30 in the morning.
你一废话就废话了十八页
And you had rambled on for 18 pages.
正反面都写满了
Front and back!
还有"你得"是指"你必须"
And by the way? Y- O- U, apostrophe R- E means, "you are. "
"你的"是代表所有格
Y- O- U- R means "your. "
我真不相信我居然还希望跟你复合
Y'know I can’t believe I even thought about getting back together again!
我们彻底完了
We are so over!
好得很
Fine by me!
顺便告诉你  那种事并不常见
And just so you know, it's not that common...
并非男人都会那样  这的确是件大事
it doesn't happen to every guy, and it is a big deal!
我就知道
l knew it!
你没有权利和他约会
You had no right to go out with him.
这真是太荒谬...
That is the most ridiculous...
-你出卖我  -我没有出卖你
- You sold me out! - l did not!
你就有出卖我  你就有
You did! You sold me... Yes you did!
让我说话好吗
Would you let me talk?
你弹了我的额头吗
Did you just flick me?
你不让我说完  我很...
OK. Well, you wouldn't let me finish and...
停下
Stop it!
-停下  -停下
- Stop. - Stop.
好  不要这样
All right. No, let's not do this.
-想想快乐的事  -不
- Happy thoughts. - No!
好  我要发威了
Okay, now l'm gonna kick some ass!
够了  你们住手  我就放手
All right. Now, l will let go if you both stop.
-好吧  -好吧
- Fine. - Fine.
这不就结了
There we go.
如果我们是在监狱里
You know what, if we were in prison,
你们都会是我的小喽罗
you guys would be, like, my bitches.
兄弟  如何啊
Okay, buddy boy, here it is.
你藏我的衣服  我就穿你全部的衣服
You hide my clothes? l'm wearing everything you own.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
看啊  我是钱德勒
Look at me, l'm Chandler!
我穿的衣服够多吧
Could l be wearing any more clothes?
或许我没穿内裤
Maybe if l wasn't going commando.
穿这么多衣服真热
l tell you,  it's hot with all of this stuff on.
我最好别做弓箭步
I ah, I better not do any, I don't know, lunges.
乔伊
Joey?
我买了乔伊特餐呢  两个披萨哦
Got you the Joey special! Two pizzas!
乔伊
Joe?
你好  又来了
Hello? Damn it!
你好
Hello?
乔伊现在不在
No, Joey's not here right now,
我应该可以帮你留言吧
but l can take a message. l think.
他还有机会  真是好消息了
He's still got a chance for the part? That's great news!
我不是说那位被狗咬伤的演员啦
Well, no, obviously not for the actor who was mauled by his dog.
太好了  我会转告乔伊  谢谢
That's great. l'll give Joey the message. Thank you.
漂亮
Yes!
好
Okay.
麦克...
Mac...
试镜...
...audition...
2点钟
...at 2:00.
过敏...
Allergy...
演员...
...actor...
遭攻击
...attacked.
被狗...
By dog...
不是...
...not...
被花
...flowers.
-请告诉我你有收到留言  -什么留言
-Please tell me you got the message. - What message?
要演麦克的演员不能演
The actor playing Mac couldn’t do it,
他们要你两点过去
they needed to see you at 2 o’clock.
什么  明明是六点
What? lt's 6:00!
我有写在留言板上
Look! l wrote it on the board!
我写在留言板上
I wrote it on the board,
然后跑遍整个纽约找你
then I went all over New York City looking for ya!
我跑去罗斯家  跑去咖啡馆
l went to Ross's, the coffee house....
跑去每一个有三明治的地方
l went to any place they make sandwiches!
-怎么这样啦  钱德勒  -对不起
- l can't believe this, Chandler! - l'm sorry.
-我不知道该说什么了  -那就说恭喜吧
- l don't know what to say! - You might say congratulations!
我看到留言板  跑去试镜  我中了
l saw the board, l went to the audition, l got the part!
你觉得很好笑吗  我刚才真的很担心
Is that supposed to be funny! I was really worried over here!
-抱歉  -有时候这样骗人很恶劣呢
- l'm sorry. - Y’know, sometimes that fake-out thing is just mean!
好吧  伙计  抱歉
Oh wow! Okay man, I’m sorry.
我不是故意要害你内疚
I did not mean to make you feel bad.
那就好
Well, that's good.
因为我没有内疚  我好替你高兴
Because you didn't! And l'm incredibly happy for you!
你好恶劣
That's mean!
-你害我惭愧  -想玩我们可以玩一天
- You had me going! - We could do this all day.
也对
Yeah, you're right.
好  我们来聊聊我以后会有多红吧
Okay look, listen, let’s talk about what a huge star I’m gonna be!
你会变成超级大明星  我要抱你
You are gonna be a huge star! I’m gonna hug ya!
-来抱吧  -好的
- You hug me! - All right.
-我们会不会太爱抱了  -我也觉得
- Do we do this too much? - l think so.
-放开我  -就是啊
- Yeah. Get off me. - Yeah.
起司  我不会扔下你的
'Come on, 'C.H.E.E.S.E., l'm not leaving without you.
你从中央处理器  启动备用电源
Route your backup power source through your CPU."
没办法  我的电路烧焦了
"l can't! My circuits are fried!
焦到不能再焦
They're fried, l tell you!"
那我就背你
"Then l'll carry you!"
好棒的招数啊
"That'll be a neat trick...
等你...
When you're...
等你死了再说
" ... when you're dead!"
罗斯  你不必用喊的
You don't have to yell.
刚才有爆炸  好吗
There was just an explosion, OK?
我的听力会受损
My hearing would be impaired.
我觉得你很棒
l thought you were excellent.
刚才我甚至觉得"怎么像换了个人演"
In fact, for a minute, l was like, "where'd Ross go?"
谢谢  我也要说
Thank you. And I have to say,
你和麦克见面的第一场戏...
that first scene where you meet Mac....
-怎样  -我的天啊  太了不起了
- Yeah? - Oh, my God. l mean....
你知道吗
And you know what?
今天就到此为止  多谢帮忙
That's enough for today. Thanks for your help.
-他欺压新人  -就是啊
- Holding us back. - Totally.